http://www.toucangallery.com/terms-and-privacy

Shop
TERMS AND CONDITIONS / PRIVACY POLICYIntroductionThis document governs the visitors and users of this website, toucanarts.com, which is owned by Toucan LLC. Various pronouns will be used to refer to this entity for simplicity’s sake.Your use of this website implies your agreement to everything stated herein, in addition to any and all applicable laws and regulations.LicenseAll original content created by Toucan LLC contained within and associated with this website is protected by applicable copyright and trademark law. All intellectual property rights are reserved.Be aware that this license is not a transfer of title.Acceptable useYou must not use this website in any way that damages or affects the use of this website by anyone, including you. And Toucan LLC.You must not use this website in any way which is illegal or fraudulent or for anything other than its intended purpose, and must never misrepresent it as anything other than what it is.DisclaimerThis website, and the materials provided in association with it, is provided “as is.” No representations or warranties, express or implied, in any regard, are made by this website or its owner.There is no warranty that this website will be available, constantly or at all; or that the information on this website is complete, or accurate, or true, or non-misleading in any way.  Limitations of LiabilityToucan LLC, its partners, and its suppliers will not be liable in relation to the contents of, or use of, or otherwise in connection with, this website and/or associated materials for any reason or in any way.These limitations of liability apply even if we, or any authorized representatives, have been notified or advised in any way of the potential liability or loss.Revisions and ErrorsWe do not warrant that any of the content of, or materials on, this website are accurate, current, or complete. Content and materials may be revised at any time without notice and there will be no commitment to updating content and materials.LinksAny links that appear on this website have not necessarily been reviewed and we are not responsible for the contents of any linked website; nor does any link found on this website imply an endorsement of the linked website. Use of any linked website is done at the user’s own risk. Be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any linked websites or websites associated in any way.Law and jurisdictionAny claim relating to this website shall be governed by the Laws of the State of Montana, without respect to its conflict of laws provisions.PrivacyYour privacy is important to us and we want you to know how we will collect and use any personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information.Re: Personally identifiable informationWe will be as transparent as possible in collecting and using personally identifiable information and will identify the purpose for which any information is being collected. Information will only be collected in order to fulfill those stated purposes unless we obtain additional consent as required. Personally identifiable information will not be retained any longer than is necessary to fulfill the stated purpose.Personally identifiable information will only be collected and used to make your access to intellectual property on toucanarts.com easier for you.Any personally identifiable information collected by us will not be shared, sold, rented, or traded with any third party. We are, however, not responsible for any personally identifiable information collected directly by a third party, even if somehow associated with this website. Personally identifiable information will be protected by reasonable and typical security safeguards on this website and in transmission from this website to your browser. This is done, obviously, through our hosting service (Squarespace, FYI), which we assume to be using all reasonable and typical security safeguards. However, in the end, we cannot guarantee the safety of your information, and by using this website you assume this risk.This website is not intended to be used by children under the age of 13 and any such use, should it occur, must be under the guidance of an adult.If you would like to review, revise, or delete any personally identifiable information we have retained about you, please send an email to toucan@toucanarts.comRe: Non-personally identifiable informationWe collect non-personally identifiable information in the way typical of most websites.In particular, this site uses “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of computer code stored on your hard drive to help improve access to and usage of this website via Squarespace, our webhost and web services provider. These cookies are also utilized in analytics provided to us via Squarespace. This use of cookies is not unique, as virtually every website does this. Usage of a cookie does not provide, nor is it linked to, any personally identifiable information. And please be aware that this site’s ability to use cookies can be modified in your browser settings, including preventing them from being used at all.ModificationsBe aware that this text may be modified at any time, including at a time after you have already read and agreed to it.
newsletter
Sign up with your email address to receive The Toucan, our email newsletter.
Email Address
Subscribe
We respect your privacy. Entering your email address will give us permission to provide you with news and updates via our email newsletter. It will not be shared, sold, or used for anything else.
Thank you!
Back to Top
TOUCAN, 2505 Montana Avenue, Billings, Montana(406) 252-0122toucan@toucangallery.com
toucan llcOPEN TUESDAY - SATURDAY
|
10 am - 4 pm2505 MONTANA AVENUE  |  BILLINGS, MONTANA  59101PHONE 406.252.0122  |   TOUCAN@TOUCANarts.COM
Terms / Privacy
